# Christopher James King

Columbus, OH - chrisking610@gmail.com - 419-936-4045 - dacking15.github.io/Personal-Website/

### **DESCRIPTION**

I am currently working remotely as the lead developer for a nonprofit named Equality Lab. My dream is to work as a gameplay programmer at a major game development studio, but would be happy to gain some experience working in a team of software developers.

## **EDUCATION**

The Ohio State University, Columbus, OH

BS in Computer Science and Engineering, 2020 Specialized in Computer Graphics and Game Design Media Marketing and Communications Scholars, Pi Kappa Phi Fraternity

## **EMPLOYMENT**

Equality Lab, Miami, Florida, June 2020 - Present, Remote

Mozilla Hubs Lead Custom Client Developer, A-Frame, Ammo.js, AWS, Blender, Bullet, Cannon.js, Git, JavaScript, Node.js, React, Spoke, Three-Ammo, THREE.js, Three Mesh UI, Wordpress. At Equality Lab, I work with a team of developers and designers from around the world to develop virtual reality experiences for USIP, Pôle emploi, and Miami Dade County Schools. As the lead developer, I have done a variety of work from setting up Hubs Cloud servers with AWS to integrating game physics into the platform.

Classroom and Digital Union Tech Support, Columbus, Ohio, January 2020 – March 2020 Sidon Lebanese Bakery and Grill, Toledo, Ohio, May 2019 – January 2020

PROJECTS: Available on my Portfolio Website

**Tanks 3D**, May 2020 – June 2020

Independent, Unity, C#, Procedural Generation, Multiplayer, Windows 10, Web GL, Xbox.

### Save the Children Presents Eyes of Mariam, January 2020 – May 2020

Collaborative, Animation Capstone, VR, Oculus Quest, Unity, C#, Windows 10, Mixamo, Xbox. *Our project was chosen by Equality Lab, our Animation Capstone sponsor, to be placed on their website and developed further for Save the Children.* 

### **COVID 19 Interactive Mirror**, January 2020 – May 2020

Collaborative, Data Visualization, HTML, CSS, JavaScript, ¡Query, D3, Excel, GitHub, Python.